Texas Governor George W. Bush:
Texas State Library and Archives Commission
- Governor George W. Bush General Counsel's settlement files, 1991-1996, bulk 1995-1996, 7 cubic ft.
  - Group two settlement files, January 1995-July 1996
    - Holdgraft, Diana vs. TNRCC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hollingsworth, Desiree vs. DHS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Holloway, Edith, 1994-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Holmes, Christina vs. DPS, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Honey, James T. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hood, Andrew J. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hortman, Sharyn and David vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Houston, La Joy vs. State of Texas, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Hubbard, Rich vs. Texas Water Development Board, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Huffman, Lawanda vs. St. Mary's Hospital, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Ivey, Walter and Shirley vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Jackson, Kerri vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Jackson, Madeline Stuart vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Glender, James vs. Texas School for the Blind and Visually Impaired, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Jaques, Linda vs. Texas School for the Blind and Visually Impaired, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Jarchow, John vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Jenkins vs. TDPRS, 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Johnson, Daniel vs. TDCJ, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Jones, Carolyn vs. DHS, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Jones, Jeffrey Construction vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Jones, Shari Ann vs. MHMR, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Juarez, Kathy vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - K., Paul, et al. vs. Donald Gilbert, et al, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Kemp, Leb and Teresa D. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Kendall, David and USAA Insurance vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Kent, Carol vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - King, Linda C. and Texas Farm Bureau Insurance Co. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - King, Melvin and Lottie Mae Butler vs. Senate, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Kirby, Gary D. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Kluza, Frank vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Kluza, Frank vs. MHMR, Abilene State School Center, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lara, Henry and Southwest Subrogation vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Laredo Housing Authority, et al. vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Larson, Patricia and Allstate Insurance Co vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Laware, Fran and David Wiley vs. Texas School for the Blind and Visually Impaired, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lawrence, Mary vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Layfield, Archie vs. Railroad Commission, 1995 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Ledbetter, Judy vs. Texas Dept. of Insurance, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lee, Gregory vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lehmann vs. Texas Employment Commission (TEC), 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lelsz, J. vs. MHMR, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lelsz, John, et al. vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Line, Harold vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lloyd, Treva vs. State of Texas, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Longoria, Nora, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lowe, Frank and Tonia vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lukens, Patricia, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Lynchard, Laurie vs. DOS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - McBride, Tonya and Fred vs. MHMR, Amarillo State Center, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - McCaskill, Paula vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - McCullough, David vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Markam, Dudley F. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Mars, Daryl vs. DPS, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Martinez, Glenda vs. DHS, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Martinez, Monica and Ruben Ochoa vs. UT Medical Branch, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Martinez, Valerie vs. TDCJ, et al, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Mathis, Melba vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Mechler, Kathleen vs. Texas Dept. of Health, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Medical indemnification [various claims], 1995-1996, [7 folders] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Memorial Hospital System vs. DHS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Mena, Guadalupe, et al. vs. George W. Bush, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Mendoza, Jaime and Grace, et al. vs. UT Medical Branch, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Miller, Katonia and Robert vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Mondata, Gonda vs. Texas National Guard, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Montez, Corina vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Moore, Heny and Allstate Insurance Co. vs. MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Morrison, Deanna vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Morse, Mary vs. State of Texas, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Murphy, James B. vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Nance, Patricia vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-326)
    - Box 3 inventory (Box 2002/151-327)
    - New, Timothy and Allstate Insurance Co. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - 1919 North Loop LP vs. Comptroller, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Nwankwo, Christina vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Ocampo, Isabel vs. TNRCC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Olguin, Richard vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Oliver, Delores vs. MD Anderson Cancer Center Outreach Corp., 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Osejo, Velma Jo vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Owens, Lisa vs. Texas Dept. of Protective and Regulatory Services (TDPRS), 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Pande, Swattie S. and P.K. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Patel, Hemendra R. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Paz, G. vs. Texas Employment Commission (TEC), 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Pekarek, Ivan vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Perry, John A. and Windsor Group vs. DPS, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Polson, Marcus (minor), 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Port of Isabel cs. GLO, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Porter, J.L., dba Evergreen Services vs. TDCJ, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Price, M., et al. vs. MHMR, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy - name of patient in mental institution] (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Putman, James vs. GLO, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - R.A.J., et al. vs. Don Denis Jones, et al, (MHMR), 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Rawls, Karen vs. TNRCC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Realy, Regina and Jason Dale Walls vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Rettberg vs. Texas Dept. of Health, 1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Riley, Sandra Annette vs. Jefferson B. Alling, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Rivera, Margaret and Ric vs. Texas School for the Deaf, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Robinson, Mike vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Robinson, Ganta N. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Robles, Stella vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Rogers, Shirley Mac vs. TEC, 1994-1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - City of Rosenberg and Frederick Hackett, et al. vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Rosendo, Juan V. vs. DPS, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Royal Inn vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Rudd, Roland H. (aka Elisha Aziz Mohammed) vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Ruiz, David vs. James Collins, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Sanford, Keith vs. MHMR (San Antonio State Hospital), 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Sampson, Alfreda vs. TABC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Sanchez, Theresa and Beatrice Al'Khathan vs. Michael R. Hammel and the Texas School for the Deaf, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Salazar, Salvador Carillo vs. TABC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Sanborn, Karen vs. TDCJ-ID Windham School, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common llaw privacy] (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Santiana, Juan Richardo vs. TNRCC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Schranne, Charles vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Serrato, J. Thomas vs. Texas Commission on Human Rights, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Seals vs. TPWD, 1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Sierra Club, et al. vs. Bruce Babbitt, et al, 1995-1996, [2 folders] (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Sharp, Timothy J.K. and wife Cheryl vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Johnny Sheraman Lincoln-Mercury vs, MHMR, 1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Smith, Carlton vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Smith, Carol vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Smith, N., et al. vs. San Antonio State Hospital, 1993-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy - name of patient in mental institution] (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Smith, Pearl vs. Texas Youth Commission, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Smith-Dorsey, Yvonne E. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Snowden, Aletha M. vs. Texas School for the Blind and Visually Impaired, 1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Solanis, Rubin vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Solis, Carmelita and Jerry vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Soliz, Rachael vs. DHS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Soza, Jesus vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Spivey, Corey vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Staples, Robert Jr., and Mary Ann Brannon vs. DPS, 1994-1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - State Farm Mutual Auto Insurance Co. vs. Texas Dept. of Agriculture, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Stewart, Laura vs. Texas Historical Commission, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Stinson, Patrick Henry vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Tabbott, Celia vs. Texas Dept. of Health and South Texas Hospital, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Taft, Barbara and State Farm Insurance Co. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Talisca, et al. vs. Burton Raiford, et al, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Tavarez, Nancy vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Taylor Butane Company vs. DPS, 1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Taylor, Theresa vs. Texas Funeral Services Commission, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Teakell, Larry and Jana vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - State of Texas vs. Gary Barnes, Texas A M University, 1992-1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - State of Texas vs. Ray W. James, 1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - State of Texas vs. Leslie Simon (Texas Dept. of Transportation), et al, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - State of Texas vs. Clarence E. Thompson, 1995, [Contains possibly excepted information: results of polygraph test] (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Texas Pharmacy Association, et al. vs. Texas Dept. of Health, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Thomas, Barbara, et al. vs. George Bush, et al, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Thomas, Shirley and Richard vs. Texas Dept. of Agriculture, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Thompson, Frederick W., et al, vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Thompson, Frederick W. vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Tillery, Suzanne and Michael vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Trevino, Robert and Mary vs. Texas State Library, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Trotter, Charles Lee vs. Texas State Highway Dept., 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Truitt, Christy vs. Texas Dept. of Agriculture, 1995 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Trulock, John B. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Turlington, Coylene vs. Office of the Attorney General, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Turner, Rona and EEOC (Equal Employment Opportunity Commission) vs. Travis State School, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Turrubiartes, Ismael vs. DPS, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - USAA vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Vaksman, Fabian vs. The Members of the Board of Regents, University of Houston, 1991, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Valle, Paul vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Van Dorn, Jim and Nedra and State Farm Mutual Auto Insurance vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Vasquez, Zulma vs. San Antonio State Hospital, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Vaughn, Edna vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Victorian, John vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Villareal, Lucia and Allstate vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-327)
    - Vistawall Plant vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Villasenor, Mary vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Wagenfuhr, Craig and Shirley vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Weaver vs. Dan Morales, Attorney General, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Weeks, Tami L. vs. TEC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Williams, Carol K. Karen and Derwin vs. GSC, 1995 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Williams, K. (a minor), 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy - name of patient in a mental hospital] (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Williams, Patricia and Jeremy vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Williams, Sonya vs. TDCJ, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Williams, Theodore vs. TDCJ, 1993-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy]; [Contains possibly excepted information: internal records of an inmate in the Dept. of Criminal Justice] (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Wilson, Debra vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Wheeler, Gene vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Whitehead, Bobby vs. TNRCC, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Wilkins, Gary vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Wyatt, Tina Marie vs. the State of Texas, 1995 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Young, Jewel vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - YoungLife vs. Texas Dept. of Transportation, 1995 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - YoungLife vs. Texas. Dept. of Transportation, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Yusuf, Wahind vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Zurita, Anthony W. vs. Texas State Technical College - Waco, 1995 (Box 2002/151-328)
  - Group three settlement files, April-September 1996
    - Box 1 inventory (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Lewis, Richard, et al. vs. Texas Dept. of Insurance, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Kuykendall, Marilyn W. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - McCook, W.E. vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Magill Truck Lines vs. TYC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Vermillion vs. Rodney W. Punch, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: name of sexual assault victim] (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Juarez vs. TDCJ, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: name of sexual assault victim] (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Thompson, Charles V. vs. John McAuliffe, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Elam, Joyce vs. TEC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Frame, Ronald vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Norton, John and Velma Ramsey vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Van Dorn, Jim and Nedra vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Flores, et al. vs. Burton Raiford (DHS), et al, 1995-1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Moore, Susan A. vs. GSC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Webster, Brian vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Household Drivers Report vs. James R. Wilson and DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Kenshalo, Sam R. and State Farm Mutual Auto Insurance vs. RRC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Rice, David E. vs. Texas Dept. of Transportation and Emilio Vela, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Ashworth, Suzanne vs. DHS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Dr. Pepper Bottling Co. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Dover Elevator vs. MHMR/Wichita Falls State Hospital, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Gallatin, Thomas, et al. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Gutierrez, Marcos vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Scott, Charlie W. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Bedford, Henry vs. Stephen P. Hannemann and TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Tucker, Christa and Preferred Risk Lloyd's Insurance Co. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Hall, Cynthia and American Protection Insurance Co. vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Oates, David L. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Taylor, Annette vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Solomon, Clara Y. vs. TPWD, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Valdez, Jose vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Williams, Rebecca P. and State Farm Mutual Auto Insurance vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Marines, Margarita, et al. vs. Herman Lambert, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Clark, Linda, Elizabeth Boswell and Margaret Moore vs. Texas Dept. of Transportation, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Gonzales, et al. vs. Kaster, et al, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Ruiz, David vs. James Collins (TDCJ) (attorney's fees), 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Avalos, George Anthony vs. Brook Elton, et al, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Pitsonbarger, Arthur vs. Charles Beard, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Castillo, Tomas, et al. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Rouse, Kimberly vs. Steven Mark Cagle and TABC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Davis, Pinkie Lou vs. DHS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Smith, Norma vs. MD Anderson Center, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Atherton, Sherry, et al. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Pesl, Joyce K. vs. GSC, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Atherton, Sherry vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Dompier, Susanna and Daniel vs. Texas Dept. of Agriculture, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Darce, Phillip A. vs. Texas School for the Blind, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Hayes, Herman vs. John Sealy Hospital, UT Health Science Center, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Lindner, Gladys L. vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Schofield, Clarence vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - R.A.J., et al. vs. Don Dennis Jones, et al. (MHMR), 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Saucier, Diane vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Nixon vs. Texas School for the Blind, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy] (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Conrad, Jack vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Keltner, Danny vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Olive, Debra vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Ramirez, Rosalinda vs. MHMR/Kerrville State Hospital, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Girard, George vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Pyle, Clifford E. and Gloria T. vs. Texas Commission on Fire Protection, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Siddon, Casey vs. Texas Workers Compensation Commission, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Lujan, Cynthia vs. San Angelo State School, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - King, Dana vs. University of Houston, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Rodgers, Heidy vs. GLO, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Hinojosa, J., et al. vs. Josue Teren, MD and Ira Doneson, MD, 1996, [Contains possibly excepted information: common law privacy - name of patient in a mental institution] (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Mendoza, Sylvia vs. Texas School for the Deaf, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Rice, Paul vs. MHMR, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Cano, Paul vs. MHMR, 1995-1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Gallatino, Thomas R., et al. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Beil, Jack B. vs. TDCJ, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Aleman, Rafael vs. DPS, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)
    - Adams, Ellen vs. Texas School for the Deaf, 1996 (Box 2002/151-328)